Guide to the Rice University Student Association records, 1918-2013 UA 252
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XII: Minutes, 149735
  - Student Association, 1966-1967; 151595 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Student Association, 1967-1968; 151596 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1968-1969; 151597 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1969-1970; 151618 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Student Association, 1970-1971; 151619 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Student Association, 1971-1972; 151620 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Student Association, 1972-1973; 151621 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Student Association, 1973-1974; 151630 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Student Association, 1974-1975; 151631 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Student Association, 1975-1976; 151632 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Student Association, 1976-1977; 151633 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Student Association, 1977-1978; 151634 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Student Association, 1978-1979; 151635 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Student Association, 1979-1980; 151636 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Student Association, 1980-1981; 151637 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1981-1982; 151638 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1982-1983; 151639 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Student Association, 1983-1984; 151640 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Student Association, 1984-1985; 151641 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Student Association, 1985-1986; 151642 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Student Association, 1986-1987; 151643 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Student Association, 1987-1988; 151644 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Student Association, 1988-1989; 151645 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Student Association, 1989-1990; 151646 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Student Association, 1990-1991; 151647 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Student Association, 1991-1992; 151648 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Student Association, 1992-1993; 151649 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Student Association, 1993-1994; 151650 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1994-1995; 151651 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Student Association, 1995-1996; 151652 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Student Association, 1996-1997; 151653 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Student Association, 1997-1998; 151654 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Student Association, 2000-2001; 151655 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Student Association, 2001-2002; 151656 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Student Association, 2002-2005; 151657 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Constitutions, 2004-2006; 151674 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Student Association, 2006-2007; 151675 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Meeting Attendance, 2006; 151676 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Summaries and Business, 2006-2007; 151677 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Student Association Aug, 2011; 151678 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Rice Fondren Buildings Exhibit Article, 2011; 151679 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Student Association Oct 17, 2011; 151680 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Student Association Oct 24, 2011; 151681 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Series XIII: General, 163738
  - Awards, 1990-1995; 163739 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1990-2003; 163740 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Constitution, 1989-1991; 163741 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Committees, 1990-2013; 163742 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Elections, 1987-2002; 163743 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Events, 1998-2005; 163744 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Members, 1988-2002; 163745 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Newsclips, 2013-; 163746 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1988; 163747 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Official stationery, 1994/1995; 163748 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Programs, 1994; 163749 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Proposals, 1988-1995; 163750 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Proposed constitutional changes, 1994-2001; 163751 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Reforms, 1998-2001; 163752 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Reports, 1988-1989; 163753 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Resolutions, 1995-2003; 163754 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Retreat, 1984-2003; 163755 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Surveys, 1994, n.d.; 163756 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Symposia, 1995-1996; 163757 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Series XIV: Minutes and Agenda, 163758
  - 1983/1984, 163760 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 1984/1985, 163761 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - 1989/1990, 163762 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - 1990/1991, 163763 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 1991/1992, 163764 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - 1993/1994, 163765 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - 1994/1995, 163766 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 1995/1996, 163767 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - 1996/1997, 163768 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - 1998/1999, 163769 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 2001/2002, 163770 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - 2003/2004, 163771 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Notes, n.d.; 163772 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Series XV: Addenda 2016
  - Sub-Series I: General
    - SA Applications/Goals, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - SA Applications, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Appointed Positions Applications, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Award, Mentor, 1971-2008 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Awards, 1991-2005 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Awards, 1993-2000 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Awards, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - College System, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Elections, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Elections, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Elections, 2000-2001 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Elections, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Elections, 2001-2009 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Elections, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Elections, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Elections, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Elections, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Elections, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Elections, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Elections, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Elections, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Guide, Committee Chair, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Guide, Senator, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Guide, Senator, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - SA Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Health Services, 1998-1999 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Homecoming Elections, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Homecoming, 2010-2011 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - KTRU, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - SA Listserv Sign Up Sheet, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Masters and Presidents Meetings, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Mtgs. with President Leebron, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - News Clipping, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Officers List, 1919-1995 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Orientation, 2000-2002 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Orientation, 2003-2005, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - O-Week Evaluation, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Parents' Weekend, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Parents/Families Weekend, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Parking, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Parking, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Parking, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Parking, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Parking, 2002-2003 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Parking, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Parliamentary Procedure, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - SA Presidents List, 1918-2014 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Report, 1966-1967 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Retreat, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Retreat, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Retreat, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Retreat, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Retreat, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Retreat, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Retreats, 2000, 2004, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Fall Retreat, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Retreat, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Retreat, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Spring Retreat, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Retreat, 2004-2005 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Fall Retreat, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Spring Retreat, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Officer Retreats, 2011 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - SA in Rice History: Reddy & Countiss, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - SA Roster, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - SA Roster, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - SA Roster, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - SA Roster, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - SilverSaver Card, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - SilverSaver Card, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Speeches, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Speeches, 2001-2002 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Speeches, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Speeches, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Speeches, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Student Organization Assistant Director, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series II: Committees
    - SA Standing Committees Report, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Committees, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Committees, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Committees, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Committees, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Committees, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Committees, 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Committees, 1995-1996 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Standing Committees, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Committees, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Committees, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Committees, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Committees, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Committees, 2007-2008 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Committee Applications, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - 9/11 Observance Committee, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Student Athlete Committee, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Committee on Athlete and Non-Athlete Relations, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Committee on Athletics, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - College Program Enhancement Committee, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Committee on Enforcement of the Alcohol Policy, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Committee on International Opportunities, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Judicial Reform, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Martel College Founding Committee, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Committee Membership, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Committee on NROTC, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - President Search Committee, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Committee of the Rice Campus Bookstore, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Rice: The Next Century, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Rice: The Next Century, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - RPC Socials Committee, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Campus Safety Committee, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Standing Committee Focus Group, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Student Alumni Liaison Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Student Alumni Liaison Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Student Alumni Liaison Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Student Alumni Liaison Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Student Organizations, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Traditions Committee, 2011 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Tuition, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Committee on Undergraduate Curriculum, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series III: Constitution
    - Constitutions and Bylaws, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Constitution, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Consitution, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Constitutions and Bylaws, 2000, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Consitution, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Consitution, 2004, 2006-2007 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Constitution, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 2013 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series IV: Memos and Correspondence
    - Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Memos, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Memos, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Memos, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Memos, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Memos, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence and Memos, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Memos and Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 2000s (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series V: Financial
    - Financials, 1988-1989 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Financial, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Financial, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Merrill Lynch Financial, 1994-1996 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Financial, 1995-1996 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Financial, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Financial, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Financial, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Financial, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Financial, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Financial, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Financial, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Financial, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Financial, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Financial, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - RPC Budget, 2010-2011 (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series VI: Legislation
    - Legislation, 1989-1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Alcohol Policy, 1990-1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Legislation, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Legislation, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Legislation, 1996-1997 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Legislation, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Legislation, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions, 2000s (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Spring Recess, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Resolution Condemning Coach Hatfield, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Legislation, 2006-2007 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series VII: Organizations
    - Rice ACLU Study Group, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Action, Reflect, Transform (ART), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - ADVANCE, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - The Aegean Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - The Rice Aerospace Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Rice African American Student Association, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - After Hours Dance Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - AIESEC Houston, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Rice Aikido Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Rice University Air-Hockey Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - The Alliance, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Alternative Medicine, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - The Rice University Amateur Radio Club (RUARC), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - American Association of Petroleum Geologists, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Americans for Informed Democracy, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - American Society for Metals, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Amnesty International, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Anderson for President Support Committee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Rice Organization for Animal Rights, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Rice Animation Organization, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Rice Anime (Jo Mai Anime), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Aphorism, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Apostolos Campus Ministry, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Rice Applied Philosophy Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - ArchiArts, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - The Architectural Society of Rice University, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Arts @ Rice, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Asian Pacific Americans for Social Action (APASA), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - The Rice Association of Biologically InclinEd Students (RABIES), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - The Rice Chapter of the Association for Computing Machinery, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Association of Students Against Sex Discrimination, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Assorted Christians Together Singing (ACTS), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Athletes in Action (AIA), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Athletic Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Rice Badminton Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Baha'i Fellowship, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Baker Gentleman's Hedonist Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - The Rice Ballet Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Ballet Folklorico, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Rice Ballroom Dance Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - The Baptist Student Union, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Youth Basketball, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Baylor-Rice Consulting & Entrepreneurial Corps, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 57)
    - Best Buddies at Rice University, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 58)
    - Beyond the Hedges, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 59)
    - Rice University Bhangra Team, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 60)
    - Biomedical Engineering Society (BMES), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 61)
    - Black Business Students Association, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 62)
    - Black Student Association (BSA), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 63)
    - Rice Blackboard Debate Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 64)
    - The Rice Board of Investors, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 65)
    - BODA Organization, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 66)
    - The Rice Boomerang Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 67)
    - The Rice Bowling Team, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 68)
    - Rice Bridge Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 69)
    - British Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 70)
    - Rice Broadcast Television, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 71)
    - Buddhist Meditation Group, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 72)
    - Bumbleplums, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 73)
    - Business Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 74)
    - Campus Crusade for Christ, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 75)
    - Campus Pagans' Alliance, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 76)
    - Canterbury Association at Rice University, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 77)
    - Rice Capitalists, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 78)
    - Cards Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 79)
    - Caribbean Student Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 80)
    - Caring Rice Students Encouraging Arts Through Education (CREATE), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 81)
    - Catholic Student Association, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 82)
    - Chabad Jewish Student Organization, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 83)
    - The Chalice, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 84)
    - CHEVRON, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 85)
    - Chi Alpha, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 86)
    - Children's Defense Fund Student Health Outreach (CDF SHOUT), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 87)
    - Chinese Students Association of Rice University, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 88)
    - Christians on Campus, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 89)
    - Christian Science Organization, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 90)
    - Churches of Christ, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 91)
    - Civic Scientists, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 92)
    - Rice U Civil Engineering Honor Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 93)
    - Class of 2001 Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 94)
    - Class of 2002 Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 95)
    - Class of 2000 PLUS, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 96)
    - Rice Club Basketball, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 97)
    - Club Chovette, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 98)
    - College Assistance Peer Program (CAPP), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 99)
    - Rice Colleges Against Cancer, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 100)
    - Cognitive Science Council, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 101)
    - Rice University College Republicans, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 102)
    - Committee Against Racism (Rice C.A.R.), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 103)
    - Committee for a Rice Community, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 104)
    - The Rice Concert Commission, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 105)
    - Rice University Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 106)
    - The Constitution of Cornerstone Christian Fellowship, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 107)
    - CSters, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 108)
    - Culinary Arts and Nutrition Club (CAN), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 109)
    - Rice Cycling Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 110)
    - The Rice Czech Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 111)
    - Dance Marathon, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 112)
    - Rice Dance Troupe, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 113)
    - Democracy Matters, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 114)
    - Rice Disc Golf Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 115)
    - Drugs!, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 116)
    - Duncan Hall Fridge Room Amendment, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 117)
    - The Eclectic Reader for Visitors to N. America, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 118)
    - Rice Education Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 119)
    - elevation: houston, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 120)
    - Elizabeth Baldwin Literary Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 121)
    - Endless Summer Surf Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 122)
    - The Energy Association at Rice, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 123)
    - Rice Energy Club Constitution, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 124)
    - The Rice Engineer, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 125)
    - The Rice University Engineering Societies Council (RECS), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 126)
    - Engineers Without Borders (EWB), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 127)
    - Rice Environmental Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 128)
    - EONFIRE at Rice, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 129)
    - ESL Tutoring Program, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 130)
    - Eta Kappa Nu, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 131)
    - Ethnographic Film Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 132)
    - The Rice Equestrian Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 133)
    - Fast Warp, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 134)
    - Rice Owl Fellowship of Christian Athletes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 135)
    - Fencing Academy, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 136)
    - Fencing Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 137)
    - Club Field Hockey n.d. (Box 25, Folder 138)
    - Film Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 139)
    - First Presbyterian College Fellowship, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 140)
    - Rice Flying Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 141)
    - Frank Zappa Literary Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 142)
    - fresh, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 143)
    - The Fresh Rice Breakers, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 144)
    - Freshman Social Committee, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 145)
    - Friends of Young Minds (FOYM), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 146)
    - Gambit: The Rice Chess Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 147)
    - GATHER, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 148)
    - G.E.E.K.S. for Enhancement of Education in Komputer Science, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 149)
    - George R. Brown Forensics Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 150)
    - German Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 151)
    - Campus Girl Scouts, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 152)
    - Rice University Global Advancement Foundation, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 153)
    - Rice Go Club, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 154)
    - Golden Key National Honor Society, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 155)
    - Rice Golf Association (RGA), n.d. (Box 25, Folder 156)
    - The Golf Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Rice Gourmet Cooking Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - The Great Books Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Rice Student Green Building Initiative, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Greens 'n' Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Gymnastics & Tumbling Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Rice University Habitat for Humanity, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Hapkido Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Rice Hayek Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - The Rice Health Care and Biotech Business Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Heritage Organization of Latin America (HOLA), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Rice Hillel, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Hindu Student Council, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - HinkJ, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Hispanic Association for Cultural Enrichment at Rice (HACER), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - The Hong Kong Student Association at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Houston Community Publishing Lectures and Forums, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Rice Houston Humane Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Humanitarian Medical Outreach, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - The Hunt, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - The Hunting and Fishing Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Club Iberoamericano, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Ideas to Action, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - IL Circolo Italiano, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Rice Independent Media, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - India Business Consortium, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - Indian Students at Rice, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Rice In-Line Skating Club (RISC), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Rice Inter Varsity Christian Fellowship, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Rice Interfaith Dialogue Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - I.A.E.S.T.E. (International Association for the Exchange of Students for Tech. Experience U.S.), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - International Chinese Undergrad Society, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Rice International Music Club, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - International Student Association, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - The International Undergraduate Society (IUS), n.d. (Box 26, Folder 35)